officefootballpool.com 2015-04-07

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Statement

This privacy statement applies to the website of:

Office Football Pool.com   
John Cranston - Website Manager   
Englewood, CO 80112   
US   
1-303-483-7560   

We respect your privacy. This is why we have taken the time to disclose our information collection practices and our privacy policy. Please take the time to review this document. 

Our focus is to provide you with great service and we totally respect your privacy.

We collect your username, password and email address when you register on the website. We don't share that information with anyone unless you are a member of a group that someone else manages. The group manager will have access to your email address and username, but not your password. Other people can see your username, but not your email address or password.

Your group leader may request that you enter other personal information into the website, like your real name, address or phone number. That information is only available to your group leader. We would never sell or give that information to anyone and we don't use that information for anything ourselves. It's strictly for your group leader's information. 

We keep track of when you log into the website and when you enter picks and we may share that information with your group leader. 

We track the number of visits to every page on our website but we don't track who visited that page. When you are browsing the website, you are anonymous. 

To log into your account on our website, your browser must accept cookies from the website. Cookies are necessary to maintain your session and stay logged in. Generally, we assign 3 cookies to your browser. Two are called CFID and CFTOKEN. The other is named something like this: Coyote-2-a500132. 

**Collecting information provides specific benefits to our website visitors:**

Collecting your email address provides us with better ability to serve you. For example, if you forget your password, the website can automatically send you a password email. We also use your email address to look up your account when you write us with questions.

**Who has access to the information we collect?**  
Your email address - You, your group leader and the website.  
Your password - You and the website.  
The time you last logged in - Your group leader and the website.  
The time you entered picks - Your group leader and the website.  
Optional personal information like real name, mailing address, phone number - Your group leader and the website. 

If you believe that our website has collected incorrect information or if you would like to dispute any information, please contact us using the address at the top of this page.
